Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/shritesh99 (LinkedIn) shri99.me/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Mobile Application Development
Data Science
Web Development

Honors-Awards

Winner at Application Development Contest

Winner in Blockchain theme at Codeutsava 3.0 hackathon, NIT Raipur

Shritesh Jamulkar

Passionate Developer | Entrepreneur | Blockchain Enthusiast Raipur

Summary

Experienced Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer and mobile gaming industry. Skilled in Native as well as Cross-Platform Application Development, Web Development, Hardware Prototyping, Game Development, Blockchain Development and much more. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Technology focused in Computer Science from National Institute of Technology Raipur.

Experience

Zenithec Techware iOS Developer May 2019 - Present (1 year 4 months) Raipur, Chattisgarh, India

Student at National Institute of Technology Raipur Student

August 2017 - Present (3 years 1 month)

Raipur Area, India

allsoft Software Developer Intern July 2019 - August 2019 (2 months)

TechFlexa
Application Developer
April 2018 - December 2018 (9 months)
Raipur Area, India

Education

National Institute of Technology Raipur

Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science · (2017 - 2021)